littleredbook.cn 2015-05-31

# Privacy Policy | Resonance

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices of Resonance China Co., Ltd (hereby referred to as Resonance).  As used in this Privacy Policy, “Service” refers to all websites, email newsletters, mobile sites, applications, and other properties or services owned or operated by Resonance. This policy may be revised or updated at any time.

By using the Services, viewing our content or research, subscribing to our newsletters, registering for a subscription account, or attending or registering for any of our events or programs, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

If you post comments, messages, or articles on the Service, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments, messages, or articles will be public. As such, Resonance is not responsible for personally identifiable information that you may choose to share through these channels.

##### What Information Do We Collect?

1) Personal information, which includes personal information you supply when you subscribe to our newsletters, register for a subscription account, create a profile, leave a comment or message, participate in one of our events, or otherwise use the Service. When you pay for certain features of the Service, Resonance, or our third party processing firm, may also collect credit card and billing information to complete the request.

2) Resonance may automatically receive and log non-personal behavioral, browsing, and device information collected during your visit to and use of the Service.

##### How We Use Personal Information

We use personal information we collect to provide, improve, and develop our Service, to tailor your user experience, to respond to your inquiries or requests, to prevent or investigate fraudulent or inappropriate usage of our Service, for research and development, to analyze trends, and for the other purposes described in this policy. In addition, we may use your email address to deliver product information and marketing messages. You may opt-out from receiving these marketing messages by following the instructions provided in the messages to unsubscribe from email communication or by emailing the address provided at the end of this policy.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you can request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by [contacting us](http://resonancechina.com/contact).

##### Third Party Links

This website may contain links to other websites that are not controlled by us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and policies of any website other than our own.

##### How do we protect your information?

We follow accepted industry standards to protect personal information you have provided. However, no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

##### Questions?

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://resonancechina.com/contact).

Scroll to top
